<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Cyber Struggle</string>

    <string name="cyber_struggle_description_1">At Cyber Struggle, We are helping cybersecurity front-liners to remain functional, resilient, and primed;
        technically and psychologically, no matter the conditions. We’ve adopted the rigor and ethos of special forces, applying it to the cyber world.
        Our training methodology centers on shifting from mere know-how to know-why, focusing on functionality. And bring the “learning” concept to the
        “acquiring” concept with experience-based simulations. We aim to cultivate experts who are problem-solvers, resilient under pressure, adaptive,
        always ready, and technically hybrid, much like special forces. This approach is not just about preparing for the current landscape of cyber
        threats but evolving with it, ensuring that our professionals are not just participants in the cybersecurity domain but leaders who define its
        future.</string>

    <string name="cyber_struggle_description_2">The landscape of warfare has evolved post-9/11, shifting from conventional armies to an unconventional
        mix of special forces and non-state actors. Similarly, cybersecurity has transformed, now dealing with threats ranging from lone wolves to
        state-sponsored groups, encompassing espionage, data theft, sabotage, privacy breaches, disinformation, and perception management.</string>

    <string name="cyber_struggle_description_3">Traditionally, the cybersecurity market approached its challenges and workforce development with a
        mindset rooted in the industrial era, focusing on technical skills, and traditional education methodologies. However, this perspective falls
        short in addressing the multifaceted nature of modern cyber threats, which are as serious and intense as they have ever been. Cyber attackers
        are not just the stereotypical hoodie-wearing antisocial figures; they represent a broad spectrum of adversaries, making the cyber domain a
        battleground for various legal and illegal entities.</string>

    <string name="philosophical_background_description">Developing interdisciplinary cybersecurity doctrine and training methodology inspired by Special
        Forces and called Ranger Program. Graduation of first 60. Heavily testing the idea.</string>

    <string name="covid_19_description">Searching the potential of implementing the online version of Ranger without losing efficiency. Aegis certification program born. Together with Ranger, the heavy test reached 250+ real customers with 99% satisfaction</string>

    <string name="s46_software_description">Some respected brands put certifications on their job description as a major plus. S46 cyber range and simulation software born and first enterprise sale. Transformation to technology startup was initiated.</string>

</resources>